ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Indoor Air Quality, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  Cornell MD/HRM, 06C#3089, 05/18/07
- SHRM, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  06C#3090, 11/14/06
- Lead Supervisor/Contractor [canceled], 2006 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  Public Program, 05C#3092, 5/2-5/06, Brown
- Lead Inspector [canceled], 2006 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  Public, 05C#3092, 6/12-14/06, Brown
- Risk Assessor [canceled], 2006 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  Public, 05C#3093, 6/15-16/06, Brown
- Technical Assist.- Ergo., 2006 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  Buffalo News, #3094
- No. 3095: Monroe County [Folder 1 of 4], 2008 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- No. 3095: Monroe County [Folder 2 of 4], 2008 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- No. 3095: Monroe County [Folder 3 of 4], 2008 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- No. 3095: Monroe County [Folder 4 of 4], 2008 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Lead Advisory Council, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  NYSDOH, #3096
- Digester Safety, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  NYSERDA, 06C#3097, 04/17/07
- Conference Module (Proposed), 2006 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  NYWEA/NYSERDA, #3098, Nov. 2006
- Lead Inspector, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  NYC DOH, 05C#3099, 6/26-28/06, Brown
- Lead Risk Assessor, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  NYC DOH, 05C#3100, 6/29-30/06, Brown
- Lead Inspector, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  NYC DOH, 05C#3101, 7/17-19/06, Brown
- Lead Risk Assessor, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  NYC DOH, 05C#3102, 7/20-21/06, Brown
- Lab Safety, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  OHM-BOCES, 06C#3103, 9/28/06
- Lead Hazards [Folders 1-4], 2006 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3104-3107, 07/10-25/06
- ASTD Speaker Info., 2006 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  #3108
- Blood-Borne Pathogens- Firefighters [Folders 1-3], 2006 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3109-3111, 07/26-31/06
- Technical Asst., 2006 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Outreach, 06C#3112, 06/20/06
- Indoor Air Quality Technical Assistance, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Fidelis Care, 06C#3113, 08/02/06; contains building floor plans
- Grace Manor- Supervisory Skills, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #3114
- Supervising for Success, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3114-3115, 6/12, 19/07, Brown
- National Carcass Disposal Symposium, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  CWMI et al, 06C#3116, 12/4-7/06
- Conference Module, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  NYWEA, 06C#3117, 02/06/07
- Occupational Stress, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Cornell MD/HRM, 06C#3118, 10/06/06
- Occupational Stress, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  Cornell MD/HRM, 06C#3119, 10/06/06
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3121, 1/23/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3122, 2/20/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3123, 3/6/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3124, 3/20/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3125, 4/3/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3126, 4/17/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3217, 5/10/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3128, 5/15/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3129, 6/5/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 06C#3130, 6/19/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3131, 7/3/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3132, 7/17/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3133, 8/7/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3134, 8/21/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3135, 9/4/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3136, 9/18/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3137, 10/2/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3138, 10/23/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3139, 11/6, 13/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3140, 11/27/07, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3141, 12/4/07, Brown
- UFCW, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3142, 04/10/07
- UFCW, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3143, 04/17/07
- Lead Inspector, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Public Program, 06C#3144, 9/11-13/06, Brown
- Risk Assessor, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Public Program, 06C#3145, 9/14/06, Brown
- Crisis Management- Albright- Knox Art Galley, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #3146, 6/18/07
- Health and Safety Committees, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3147, 05/17-16/07
- City of Buffalo [Folder 1-12], 2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3148-3159, 10/17-26/06
- Farm Digester Tech. Asst., 2007 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3160, 09/06/07
- Farm Digester- Shetland Farm, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3161, 04/23/08
- Health and Safety: RIT, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  SUNY Cobleskill, 06C#3162, 11/13/06
- Contemporary Labor Issues- Guest Lecture, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  Buffalo Labor Stories, #3163, 2/8/7
- Disaster Site Worker Training, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  IUOE, 06C#3164, 69/23/07
- Hazmat Refresher [Folders 1-7], 2007 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  IUOE, 06#3165-3171, 02/08-16/07
- Risk Assessor, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  NYC DOH Bureau of Day Care, 06C#3176, 10/26-27/06, Brown
- Weatherization Project, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  Apollo Alliance, #3172
- Village Elementary- Indoor Air Quality, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3173, 11/08-09/06
- Northwood Elementary- Indoor Air Quality, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #3174, 11/15/06
- Lead Inspector, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  NYC DOH Bureau of Day Care, 06C#3175, 10/23-25/06, Brown
- Article- Crisis Management, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  HR Encyclopedia, #3177, 03/02/11
- Stress, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  MD/HRM, 06C#3178, 12/12/06
- Occupational Stress, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  MD/HRM, 06C#3179, 11/07/06
- NYSUT Conference- Br. Cancer, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3180, 06/10/07
- United Way- Tech. Asst., 2007 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3181, 03/07/07
- UAW-55, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #3182, 04/19/07
- Workplace Violence, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #3183, 01/23/07
- Risk Assessor Refresher [canceled], 2007 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  Public, 06C#3184, 1/22/07, Brown
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  Public, 06C#3185, 2/21/07, Brown
- Indoor Air Quality, Tech. Asst. (Proposed), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  Cayuga S.D., #3186
- MCWA- Respiratory and PPE, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3187, 01/31/07
- MCWA- Respiratory Protection and PPE, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3188, 02/28/07
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  Madison County Department of Health, 06C#3189, 1/7/07, Brown
- Interview, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  Marketplace Radio, 06C#3190, 01/03/07
- Tech. Asst., 2007 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3191, 02/02/07
- Crisis Management- NYWEA, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, 06C#3192, 04/03/07
- Crisis Management, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #3193, 10/02/07
- Crisis Management, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3194, 10/03/07
- Crisis Management, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  NYWEA, 07C#3195, 10/04/07
- Hazard Analysis, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  Owens-Corning, 06C#3203, 04/26-27/07
- Lead Inspector, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  NYC DOH- Bureau of Day Care, 06C#3217, 5/7-9/07, Brown
- Tech. Asst.- Benzene/Coke Ovens, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  Lipsitz, Green Esq., #3252, 07/06/07
- Indoor Air Quality- Tech. Asst., 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Ciminelli, 07C#3253, 07/24/07
- Mold Exposure, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  P. Beltz, P.C., #3254, 06/29/07
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Public, 07C#3255, 9/19/07
- No. 3256: Ventilating Manure Storage [Folder 1 of 2], 2007-2011 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- No. 3256: Ventilating Manure Storage [Folder 2 of 2], 2007-2011 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Public, 07C#3257, 9/5/07
- Tech. Asst.- Carbon Monoxide in Warehouse, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Ciminelli, #3258, 07/30/07
- Hazcom, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3259, 09/18/07
- Hazcom, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3260, 09/19/07
- Hazcom, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3261, 09/20/07
- Indoor Air Quality- 1st Niagara, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  Ciminelli, 07C#3262, 08/17/07
- CISD, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  NYWEA, #3263, 02/05/08
- OSHA Training Inst. RRP, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  #3264
- Compost Safety and Health Factsheet, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  CWMI, #3265
- NYWEA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3266, 04/10/08
- Work, Health, and Health Care, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  Cornell ILR Grad Programs, 07C#3267, 02/12/08
- City of Buffalo, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3268, 10/22/07
- City of Buffalo, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3269, 10/23/07
- City of Buffalo, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3270, 10/23/07
- No. 3271: Blood Borne Pathogens, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- City of Buffalo [Folders 1-8], 2007 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3272-3279, 10/25/07-11/01/07
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3280, 03/04/08
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3281, 03/12/08
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3282, 04/09/08
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3283, 04/16/08
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3284, 05/07/08
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3285, 05/14/08
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3286, 06/04/08
- MCWA, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3287, 06/11/08
- Occupational Stress and Shiftwork, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  CSEA, #3288, 04/26/08
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3289, 1/22/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3290, 2/19/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3291, 3/11/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 07C#3292, 3/25/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant), 07C#3293, 4/8/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant), 07C#3294, 4/29/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant), 07C#3295, 5/13/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant), 07C#3296, 5/27/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant), 07C#3297, 6/10/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant), 07C#3298, 6/24/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant 574-8602), 08C#3299, 7/15/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant 574-8602), 08C#3300, 7/29/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant 574-8602), 08C#3301, 9/08/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant 574-8602), 08C#3302, 8/26/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant 574-8602), 08C#3303, 9/9/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health (Grant 574-8602), 08C#3304, 9/23/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3305, 10/7/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3306, 10/28/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3307, 11/11/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3308, 11/26/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3309, 12/9/08, Brown
- International Grant (Proposal), 2007 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  Cornell ILR, #3310
- Lead Sampling Technician (Proposal), 2007 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  NYC Dept. of Health, #3311
- Workplace Violence, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  Cornell Labor Studies, 07C#3312, 11/08/07
- Hazmat Refresher [Folders 1-4], 2008 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  IUOE, #3313-3316, 02/04-19/08
- Digester Safety and Health- Conference, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  NIFS, #3342, 06/25/08
- Lead Worker, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  MCDPA, #3345, 04/30/08-05/01/08
- Confined Space for Chautauqua County, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #3354, 1/02/08
- Confined Space and Agricultural Hazards, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #3355, 12/03/08
- Conference Module on Chem's and Breast Cancer Risk, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  FSWNYS, #3373, 9/20/08
- Conference Module on Chem's and Breast Cancer Risk, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  FSWNYS, 08C#3374, 9/20/08
- Lab Safety for OHM-Boces, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3375, 05/26/10
- Conference Module: Hazard Evaluation, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  NABEC, 08C#3376, 07/28/08
- Inspector Initial, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  NYC Dept. of Health, 07C#3381, 4/21-23/08, Brown
- Risk Assessor Initial, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  NYC Dept. of Health, 07C#3382, 04/24-25/08, Brown
- Zonta- Stress, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3389, 09/16/08
- ECR, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3402, 06/13/08
- Lead Worker Training, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, 07C#3403, 6/25-26/08, Brown
- LSWPs, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  Cayuga County Coop Ext., #3404, 10/29/08
- Health and Safety Composting, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  US Composting Council, #3405, 01/26/09
- Tech. Asst., 2008 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  MCWA, 07C#3406, 04/16/08
- Trainer on Health and Safety, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #3407, 10/21-22/08
- Shiftwork (On-line), 2008 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  Cornell L.E.L., #3408, 11-12/08
- Tech Asst.- Indoor Air Quality, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  First Niagara Bank, 08C#3409, 06/24/08
- FFs [Folders 1-4], 2008 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3410-3413, 09/08-12/08
- Confined Space- NYWEA, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3414, 10/07/08
- Confined Space- NYWEA, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3415, 10/08/08
- LSWPs- Action for Better Community, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #3416, 08/25/08
- Risk Assessor Refresher, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  Public, 08C#3417, 1/14/09
- Interview, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  Las Vegas Sun, #3418, 06/30/08
- NYWEA, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  #3419, 02/03/09
- Blood Borne Pathogens- N.F., 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3420, 10/29/08
- Blood Borne Pathogens- N.F., 2008 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3421, 10/29/08
- Blood Borne Pathogens- N.F., 2008 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3422, 10/30/08
- Blood Borne Pathogens- N.F., 2008 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3423, 10/30/08
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3424, 1/10/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3425, 2/17/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3426, 3/10/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3427, 3/24/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3428, 4/07/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3429, 4/24/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3430, 04/25/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3431, 5/05/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3432, 5/22/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3433, 5/23/09
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health,, 08C#3435, 6/26/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 08C#3435, 6/26/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3436, 6/27/09, Brown
- Lead Safety, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3440, 8/11/09, Brown
- Lead Safety, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3442, 8/29//09, Brown
- Lead Safety, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3443, 9/15/09, Brown
- Lead Worker Training, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  Public (Monroe County Grant), 07C#3345, 3/26-27/08, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3437, 7/7/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3438, 7/24/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3439,7/25/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3441, 8/28/09, Brown
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3444, 9/29/09, Brown
- No. 3445: Barbershops/Cosmetology [Folder 1 of 7], 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- No. 3445: Barbershops/Cosmetology [Folder 2 of 7], 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- No. 3445: Barbershops/Cosmetology [Folder 3 of 7], 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- No. 3445: Barbershops/Cosmetology [Folder 4 of 7], 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- No. 3445: Barbershops/Cosmetology [Folder 5 of 7], 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- No. 3445: Barbershops/Cosmetology [Folder 6 of 7], 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- No. 3445: Barbershops/Cosmetology [Folder 7 of 7], 2004-2013 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Tech. Asst.- Indoor Air Quality, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  Public Service, #3446, 05/09/08
- H2S Tech. Asst., 2007 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  Cayuga County Coop. Ext., #3447, 12/07-
- Hazard Reduction for Composting, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  US Composting Council, #3448, 1/28/09
- Consumer Resource Guide, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  #3449
- Teachers and Chem. Expos., 2009 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  #3450
- Health and Safety Issues/Regulations/Techniques, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  SUNY at Cobleskill, 08C#3451, 10/09/08
- Work-Relatedness, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  ILR (Resident), 08C#3452, 10/15/08
- "Green" Jobs (Proposed), 2008 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  WIED, #3453
- No. 3454: Hazard Communication [Folder 1 of 2], 2008 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- No. 3454: Hazard Communication [Folder 2 of 2], 2008 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Hazard Communication/PPE, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3455, 10/28/08
- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3456, 09/23/08
- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3457, 09/23/08
- NYWEA, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #3458, 05/27/09
- Urban Community Corp/Lead Safe Work Practices, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3459, 11/12/08
- UCC- Mold, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, #3460, 23/09/08
- Pesticide Conference, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #3461, 03/16/09
- Confined Space and Agricultural Hazards, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #3462, 12/16/08
- UFCW, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #3463, 04/14/09
- UFCW, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #3464, 04/08/09
- "Work, Health, and Health Care" Course, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  Cornell ILR Resident/Ext. Collaboration, #3465, 02/12/09
- Nail Salon Workers (Proposal), 2008 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  Cornell Institute for Women and Work- WIED, #3466,
- DeGraff Daycare- Indoor Air Quality, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3467, 09/17/08
- City of Buffalo, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3468, 10/14/08
- City of Buffalo [Folders 1-11], 2008 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#2469-3479, 10/14/08-11/07/08
- Buffalo- Food Service, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3481, 02/04/09
- Buffalo- Food Service, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #3482, 02/17/09
- Hazmat Refresher, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  IUOE, #3483, 02/09/09
- Hazmat Refresher, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  IUOE, 02/11/09, #3485
- Hazmat Refresher, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  IUOE, #3484, 02/10/09
- Disaster Site Worker, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  IUOE, #3486, 02/19/09
- Hazmat Refresher [Folders 1-10], 2009 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  IUOE, #3487-3496, 02/23/09-03/13/09
- Hazmat Initial, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  IUOE, #3497, 02/05/09
- Disaster Site Worker, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  IUOE, #3498, 02/27/09
- Hazmat Refresher [Folders 1-5], 2009 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  IUOE, #3499-3503, 02/20/09-03/06/09
- No. 3504: Cornell Manure Management [Folder 1 of 5], 2008-2013 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- No. 3504: Cornell Manure Management [Folder 2 of 5], 2008-2013 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- No. 3504: Cornell Manure Management [Folder 3 of 5], 2008-2013 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- No. 3504: Cornell Manure Management [Folder 4 of 5], 2008-2013 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- No. 3504: Cornell Manure Management [Folder 5 of 5], 2008-2013 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Hazmat Initial, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  IUOE, #3505, 02/18/09
- Breast Cancer in Female Firefighters, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  Int'l Association of Women in Fire Emergency Services, #3506 (see #2860), 05/15-16/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #3507, 01/13/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #3508, 02/17/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #3509, 03/24/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #3570, 04/14/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, #3511, 05/20/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, #3512, 06/09/09
- Lead Safe Work Practices, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, #3513, 03/04/09
- CNYCOSH (Proposal), 2008 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  #3514
- Hazcom, Noise, PPE for MCWA, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  WNYCOSH, 08C#3515, 11/11/08
- Tech. Asst.- Pelletizer, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  SUNY Cobleskill, #3516, 12/04/08
- Hazcom, Noise, PPE for MCWA, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, #3517, 11/19/08
- NYS Poll Prev. Grant- Hilton S.D., 2008 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #3518, 11/2008-
- Hilton School District- Indoor Air Quality, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #3519, 12/10/08
- Health and Safety Committee Skills, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #3520, 03/23/09
- Firefighters- Thermal Decomposition, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #3521
- Indoor Air Quality Tech. Asst., 2008 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Ciminelli, #3522, 11/13/08
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #3523, 05/12/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #3524, 01/20/09
- Erie County, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #3525, 06/03/09
- Lead Safety for RR and P, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3256, 10/13/09, Brown
- Lead Safety, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 09C#3527, 10/27/09, Brown